(Bernadette:)Howie.
(Howard:)Penny has a message for you.
l heard.
(Bernadette:)Your voice, not unlike your mother's,
travels through walls.
(Howard:)Do you want me to go?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Bernadette:)Come here.
(Bernadette:)- I'm still really mad at you.
- l get that.
(Bernadette:)Anything else about your past
l should know?
Couple of things, but most of them
happened overseas. I'll tell you later.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Howard:)So is the wedding still on?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, the wedding's still on.
Thank God, I'm still a maid of honor.
Oh, what the hell?
(Amy:)This is kind of hot.
(Leonard:)Hello.
(Penny:)What's with the robe?
I'm going to have sex with you right here
right now on that washing machine.
(Penny:)No, you're not.
Come on, please?
You wanna do something,
you can help me fold this sheet.
(Leonard:)Folding a sheet in my underwear...
(Leonard:)...still pretty crazy.